Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Yeah. baby.
Hi. I'm Dixie.
Dixie Normous.
I may just be a small-town
FBI agent slash single mother.
but I'm still tough and sexy.
Well. Miss Normous.
shall we shag now.
or shag later?
Oh. Austin. behave.
Hey. Powers.
You better watch your frigging self.
because this is one doctor
who does make house calls.
Right. Mini-Me?
Hey. assholes.
I'm right over here.
I'm Mini-Me.
Come and get me.
And cut.
That's a cut. everybody.
Moving on. Check the gate. please.
So. Austin. what'd you think
of the opening credits?
Well. I can't believe Sir Steven Spielberg.
the grooviest filmmaker
in the history of cinema.
is making a movie about my life.
Very shagadelic. baby. Yeah.
Having said that.
I do have some thoughts.
Really?
My friend here.
thinks it's fine the way it is.
Well. no offense. Sir Stevie.
but you've got to have mojo. baby. Yeah.
Hit it.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Mr. Quincy Jones.
Yeah.
This is where the movie
gets its mojo. baby.
Groovy. yes.
Quiet. everybody.
Music video. take two.
It's Britney Spears.
I did it again. baby.
Yeah.
I love you!
Welcome back. Herr Doktor.
How was space?
Space was cool.
Wasn't it. Mini-Me?
Yeah.
Dr. Evil. while you were in space
I created a way for us to make
huge sums of legitimate money
and still maintain the ethics
and the business practices
of an evil organization.
I have turned us into a talent agency.
The Hollywood Talent Agency.
Really?
By charging A-list clients 9 percent.
rather than the traditional 10 percent.
we've been able to sign such stars
as George Clooney.
Julia Roberts
Hey.
And Leo DiCaprio.
Leo.
And the best part
of the whole scheme is.
we all get our own assistants.
Hi. I'm Number Three.
I'm really excited to be part
of the team here at HTA.
Very impressive. Number Two.
But I finally have the perfect plan.
In the '70s there lived
a Dutch metallurgical hedonist
by the name of Johann van der Smut.
He loved gold so much
he even lost his genitalia
in an unfortunate smelting accident.
Hence the name...
Goldmember.
He invented a cold-fusion power unit.
for a tractor beam...
Tractor beam.
powerful enough to pull
a meteor to Earth.
The meteor was called...
Midas 22.
It's made of solid gold.
Is he sleeping?
Well. that's ok.
I guess Mini-Me
won't get any chocolate!
You want down. Mini-Me?
Use your words like a big boy clone.
He's ok.
Here's the chocolate.
It's from Bruges.
That's in Belgium.
That's where Daddy's from.
Yeah.
Check out Mini-Me.
Yeah. He's gone mental
on account of the chocolate.
It's like fricking catnip for clones.
Your chair. Dr. Evil.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Skedaddle. Right.
You know. when you have kids
I think you're gonna find
that all kids are different?
For example.
Mini-Me loves chocolate.
Scotty don't.
What. I like chocolate fine. I just...
How about you. this is very familiar.
Hang on. let me do what I do.
Would you stop?
How about I what?
I don't even...
Honestly. isn't this...
How about you don't?
Ladies and gentlemen. Scotty don't.
Dr. Evil. perhaps it's time that
you finished unveiling your plan.
Yes. thank you. Number Two.
Ladies and gentlemen. my plan is...
Scotty don't.
Oh. come on. you're such a lame-ass.
Mini-Me aime les Chocolats...
Scotty n'aime pas.
Yeah.
Oh. so...
Oh. so we're...
You know. this is causing me
serious psychological harm.
I don't know.
Who am I?
Fine. you know what?
I would love some chocolate.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Perfect.
Heel. Mini-Me.
Heel.
Come on. got me a marlin.
Yeah.
You ok. Mini-Me?
Yeah? Did I pull too hard?
I don't want to hurt you.
Dr. Evil.
Yeah?
What does Goldmember's plan
have to do with us?
Our early attempts at a tractor beam
went through several preparations.
Preparations A through G were a failure.
But now. ladies and gentlemen
we finally have a working tractor
beam. which we shall call.
Preparation H.
What?
Why don't you just call it
Operation Ass Cream. you ass.
I'm sorry. did you want some ice cream?
Yes.
I'd love some chocolate ass cream.
Perhaps later.
Dr. Evil. I love your plan.
Yeah?
Ja. Herr Doktor. it's a really good plan.
Yes. Frau. on the whole.
I think Preparation H feels good.
What is it now?
No. nothing. you know what. I agree.
Preparation H does feel good
on the hole.
Well. I'm glad we're sprechen Sie
the same lingitty. Ja.
Ladies and gentlemen.
using my time machine.
I shall travel back to 1975.
pick up Goldmember
and bring him back to the future.
And the best part of this plan is...
No one can stop me.
Not even.
Austin Powers.
Not so fast.
You're surrounded. Dr. Evil.
Shit.
Dr. Evil. the World Court
sentences you to 400 years.
Do you have anything to say?
No. but I think Mini-Me does.
Order!
I will have order!
Looks like two eggs in a hanky.
The criminal genius known as Dr. Evil
and his clone
were sentenced today
at the World Organization.
For his efforts. Austin Powers
son of England's most famous spy.
Nigel Powers
will be knighted by the queen
at Buckingham Palace.
Arise. Sir Austin Powers.
Thank you. Your Majesty.
Your father must be very proud of you.
Oh. yeah.
Come on. Dad. stand up
and take a bow.
Daddy?
Dad?
♪ Daddy. ♪
♪ Daddy wasn't there. ♪
♪ To take me to the fair. ♪
♪ It seems he doesn't care. ♪
♪ Daddy wasn't there. ♪
♪ When I was first baptized. ♪
♪ When I was criticized. ♪
♪ When I was ostracized. ♪
♪ When I was Jazzercised. ♪
♪ Steak and kidney pies. ♪
♪ One-hour Martinize. ♪
♪ When I was circumcised. ♪
♪ Daddy wasn't there. ♪
♪ To take me to the fair. ♪
♪ To change my underwear. ♪
♪ Daddy wasn't there. ♪
Daddy Wasn't There. Peace.
I am a sexy beast.
Yes.
Bangs.
Yes. how's it going?
The robot.
Haven't seen that in a while.
It's Austin Powers!
You so funny.
Well. you know.
Also. very sexiful.
Can I have autograph?
Of course.
Your name is?
Fook Mi.
Oh. behave. baby.
Yes.
Now. your name is?
Fook Mi.
You kiss your mother with that mouth?
Like this.
Oh. I see!
Your name is Fook Mi.
You want drink?
Yes. of course.
But you know. I I...
I have a private bar.
in the back that you're more
than welcome to use.
Here you go.
But...
Fook Mi. that was fast.
Fook Yu.
You're going the right way
for a smacked bottom
and I don't care who knows it.
Austin.
This is my twin sister.
Her name Fook Yu.
Fook Yu.
Fook Mi.
See?
Twins. Twins.
Twins. Yes.
We're going to see the twins. Yes.
I also think Austin Powers very sexiful.
We think you are very gravy. baby.
Do we make you sleepy?
Well. you make me many things.
but sleepy's not one of them.
We give you top-secret massage.
Yes. top-secret massage. baby.
Sorry about that.
I swear to God that never happens.
Yes. hold on a tic.
Ok.
Ok. now. where were we. babies? Yes.
Austin.
I'm sorry to interrupt.
Twins. Basil.
Twins.
Austin. it's your father.
Bye-bye.
What?
He's been kidnapped.
Very heavy. man.
So that's why my father wasn't
at the knighting ceremony.
Well. no. actually.
He was kidnapped after
you were knighted.
He was last seen on his yacht.
Yes. the HMS Shag-at-Sea.
Exactly.
Just take a look.
Gentlemen. fall in.
Austin. these men were assigned
to guard your father.
Ok. chaps.
Chins up. trousers down.
I think we may have found a clue.
Cor blimey.
All your privates have had
their privates painted gold.
How bizarre.
Imagine. gilded tallywhackers
golden wedding tackle.
14-karat trouser snakes...
That's enough.
Ok.
Basil. there is only one
person in the world
who truly understands
the psychology of a madman.
Dr. Evil.
I've been expecting you. Mr. Powers.
My father is missing.
Yes. I heard.
How ironic.
You finally caught me.
yet now you need me more than ever.
But then again.
you've always needed me.
haven't you. Mr. Powers?
Remember when I told you
we're not so different. you and I?
We're not so different. you and I.
See?
I did say that.
Very clever.
Now. who has my father?
Someone has some daddy issues.
Nothing could be my father
from the truth.
You said my father.
No. I dadn't.
Didn't. Did not.
For me. this is a dad issue.
Dead issue.
Dead dad.
Deadbeat dad.
Daddy didn't love me.
It seems the knighting ceremony
wasn't the only time your...
daddy let you down.
Remember that day at the academy?
Think.
It was graduation.
Yeah. baby. yeah.
Do I make you horny. baby?
Oh. yes. that's the spot.
Right there.
You're a naughty one.
Yes. you are.
Hello. vicar.
Crake!
Have you ever heard
of knocking. man?
Right.
We were just getting started.
Bye. love.
Don't forget Master Powers.
later you have a brief oral exam.
Well. I hope it's mostly
oral and not too...
brief. baby.
You know. brief and oral exam.
Marks are in. lads.
It looks Like Master Evil
is the top contender
for this year's International
Man of Mystery.
He's number one in the class.
Whoop-de-do. Basil.
Hey.
Everybody. I'm number one.
Who cares?
Hello. I'm Number Two.
Nice to meet you. Number Two.
but now I'm going to be named
this year's International Man of Mystery.
Yeah. right.
Shut your gob.
Who throws a cupcake?
Honestly.
And now it's time
to award our greatest honor.
This year's International
Man of Mystery is...
Austin Powers.
Well done. Austin.
Jolly good.
Top notch.
We're proud of you.
Very well done. indeed.
It's always been my dream
to win this award. just like my dad.
And I'm glad he could be here.
Stand up. Dad.
Take a bow.
Dad?
Daddy?
Boo-frickity-hoo.
I had the best grades in the class
and I didn't get diddlysquat.
Here we go.
Tell me. Mr. Powers.
what did you find on those sailors?
A golden surprise. perhaps?
How did...
Yes.
All the sailors had their
meat and two veg painted gold.
Yes. it's the distinctive calling card
of a criminal mastermind.
The aptly named...
Goldmember.
How can I find this Goldmember?
Quid pro quo. Mr. Powers.
Yes. squid pro row.
I'll give you Goldmember.
you give me a transfer
to a regular prison.
so that I could be with
my beloved. Mini-Me.
Ok. I'll get you a transfer
to a regular prison.
Now. where's Goldmember?
Not where. Mr. Powers.
but when.
1975. Studio 69 Disco.
New York City.
Corner of 69th and 8th.
You go now. Mr. Powers.
Fly. fly.
I'll get it.
Instead of hiding your father
in some remote location.
Goldmember is hiding him in 1975.
So our engineers have crafted
this vehicle.
to time-travel to the '70s.
Smashing. Basil.
A pimpmobile.
Oh. yes. yes.
I knew it would tickle your fancy.
What can I say?
Look.
Cough.
Here we go. 1975.
Good luck. Austin.
1975!
Yeah. baby!
Yeah!
♪ Solid Gold. ♪
♪ It's gold. it's gold. ♪
♪ It's solid gold. baby. ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
♪ He's got the Midas touch. ♪
♪ But he touched it too much. ♪
♪ Hey. Goldmember. ♪
♪ He's got a golden pad. ♪
♪ He's super bad. ♪
♪ Hey. Goldmember. ♪
Good evening everybody.
and welcome to Studio 69.
Here he is. ladies and gentlemen.
It's Goldmember!
Hey. everybody.
I am from Holland.
Isn't that weird?
Yes.
♪ He's got the Midas touch. ♪
♪ But he touched it too much. ♪
♪ Hey. Goldmember. Yeah. ♪
♪ Hey. Goldmember. ♪
♪ You're getting down tonight. ♪
♪ You're dynamite. ♪
♪ Hey. Goldmember. ♪
♪ Goldmember. ♪
♪ Because that's the way. ♪
♪ Aha. Aha. ♪
♪ He likes it. ♪
♪ Goldmember. ♪
♪ He loves it. ♪
♪ Because that's the way. ♪
♪ Aha. Aha. ♪
♪ He likes it. ♪
♪ Goldmember. ♪
♪ He loves it. ♪
♪ He's got the Midas touch. ♪
♪ He touched it too much. ♪
♪ Hey. Goldmember. ♪
♪ Goldmember. ♪
♪ He's from the Netherlands. ♪
♪ It's where he learned to dance. ♪
♪ Hey. Goldmember. ♪
♪ Gold. Goldmember. ♪
♪ It's gold. it's gold. ♪
♪ It's solid gold. baby. ♪
♪ Goldmember's so solid. ♪
♪ It's gold. it's gold. it's gold. ♪
♪ It's gold. ♪
♪ It's solid gold. baby. ♪
♪ His member's so gold. ♪
♪ Yes. it is. yeah. ♪
Well. if it isn't Austin Powers.
I'm sorry?
You got a lot of nerve dragging
your jive white ass in here.
I don't believe we've met.
It's me.
Foxxy!
Foxxy Cleopatra!
Long time. no see.
Stop!
We can't be seen talking
to each other. you dig?
I'm using this cat as a distraction.
I get it.
Yes. very clever.
First things first.
Kabibble!
Eight years and no phone call?
Nobody stands up Foxxy Cleopatra!
Where have you been?
Listen. Foxxy.
I just want you to know
I never intended to hurt you. baby.
Well. all I know is...
Mama only got a taste of honey.
but she wanted the whole beehive.
Oh. beehive.
Yes. beehive.
You always knew how
to make me smile.
Well. you know. it's a gift. really. I...
What am I doing?
Foxxy.
what are you doing
in Goldmember's club?
I'm undercover.
About a year ago.
my partner at the bureau was killed.
And that jive-ass turkey Goldmember
is the prime suspect.
Your father's in the back room.
under heavy guard.
Thanks. Foxxy.
Austin!
Good luck.
Dad!
Hello. son.
Just. overpowering my guards.
I'm here to rescue you.
Come quickly.
I've got a better idea.
why don't you rescue me
in about. what.
seven or eight minutes. he said.
Oh. knock it off.
I don't want to see
my dad on the job.
Come on. let's go.
Ok. I'm sorry. I'm sorry girls.
No.
I've got to go. it's my boy.
Hold on.
What's wrong with your neck?
I took a Viagra.
It got stuck in my throat.
I've had a stiff neck for hours.
I thank you.
Listen Dad. if you are gonna
talk about naughty things
in front of these American girls
then at least speak English English.
Alright. my son.
Oh. God. we had some good times?
We had some good times?
Wonderful times. we had.
Good times. yeah.
We had some good...
times.
Welcome to 1975.
Austin Powers and father.
Excuse me while I change.
The roller boogie has made me sweaty.
Yeah.
You see Mr. Powers
I love gold.
The look of it. the taste of it.
the smell of it. the texture.
I love gold so much.
that I even lost my genitalia
in an unfortunate smelting accident.
Hence the name.
Goldmember.
We are both swingers. you see?
You have a tight body.
Yes.
I see that from your tight pants.
Yes. you are tight. like a tiger.
Would you like a smoke and a pancake?
A what?
A smoke and a pancake.
You know?
Flapjack and a cigarette?
Alright.
Cigar and a waffle. no?
Pipe and a crepe?
No?
Bong and a blintz?
No.
Oh well...
Then there is no pleasing you.
That's not right.
Hello.
What have we here?
That's a keeper.
Yes.
Put it in the skin box. please.
With the others.
I'm peeling.
Oh. that's just disgusting.
Quickly.
Quickly. thank you.
Save me from myself.
You're insane. Goldmember.
♪ And that's the way. ♪
♪ Aha. Aha. ♪
♪ I like it. ♪
KC and the Sunshine Band.
Alright Goldmember.
Don't play the laughing boy.
There are only two things
I can't stand in this world.
People who are intolerant
of other people's cultures...
and the Dutch.
What?
Take the father away.
Dutch-hater.
And now...
it is time to say goodbye.
Dr. Evil's orders.
Which for you is bad news. bears.
Walter Matthau.
Shazam.
Up yours jive turkey.
Traitor.
Yes. the gun.
Good. very good.
2002.
They're taking my father
to the time machine.
The say-what machine?
Come on. now.
No! Let's Go!
This way. sugar.
That was close. Foxxy.
I owe you one.
Austin. I found this in Goldmember's office.
It's a microfilm. it may be a clue.
Smashing.
I want to go to the future with you.
We can catch Goldmember together.
I owe it to my partner.
I should warn you. Foxxy.
2002 is very different.
Well...
the future better get ready for me.
Because I'm Foxxy Cleopatra.
and I'm a whole lot of woman.
2002. here we come.
All visitations limited to five minutes.
No spitting in the visitors room.
Herr Doktor.
I have some news.
It's your son.
He wants to take over
the family business.
Scotty does?
He's gotten so evil.
he has even started losing his hair.
I know. it's sweet.
Oh he just wants to make
you proud. Herr Doktor.
After all it's hard on the boy
not having a father.
You know.
first you were frozen. then you were in space.
now you're in jail.
Well. don't tell me he feels neglected.
I was adopted by fricking Belgians?
You were adopted?
I never met my birth parents.
There was a car accident.
I'm told it was a beautiful Belgian day.
The smell of waffles and Brussels sprouts
filled the summer air...
until.
My birth mother was incinerated.
I only survived
because her smoking carcass
formed a protective cocoon
of slaughtered human effluence.
A Belgian man and his 15 year old
love slave with webbed feet
was looting the accident scene.
They came across a blood
soaked baby. moi.
They raised me to be evil.
You know. that old chestnut.
Yeah.
But nothing compares to this.
being inside the belly of the beast
night after night. all alone.
Daddy's all pent up.
Let's freak!
Time's up.
Visiting hours are over.
Step to the line.
Cuffs up.
Move it.
Hi. there.
How you sleeping good?
Gentlemen.
listen up. y'all.
Here's the new plan.
You're gonna start a riot.
and we're gonna
walk out the front door.
Hey. man.
I know guys on crack
that makes more sense than you.
Really?
Then let me put it
to you this way. cuz.
♪ Yeah. ♪
♪ Instead of treated ♪
♪ We get tricked ♪
♪ Instead of kisses ♪
♪ We get kicked ♪
♪ It's the hard knock ♪
♪ I don't know how to be ♪
♪ No crib on MTV ♪
♪ God only knows ♪
♪ Got my Mini-Me in the G.P. ♪
♪ See how it goes ♪
♪ Evil's all that I see ♪
♪ And you ask me my name? ♪
♪ D to the rizzo ♪
♪ E to the vizzo ♪
♪ I to the lizzo ♪
♪ I'm a crazy ♪
♪ Y'all knew that ♪
♪ Austin caught me in the first act ♪
♪ It's all backwards. what's with that? ♪
♪ So I'll make a prophecy ♪
♪ From the dogs to the Mini-Me ♪
♪ Give me an Escalade. a two-way ♪
♪ Bling bling on eBay ♪
♪ Domino ♪
♪ Stick that in your pipe and smoke it ♪
♪ Instead of treated ♪
♪ This is for all my homeys in Bruges ♪
♪ Cristal. ♪
♪ My Moto. ♪
♪ A couple of beyotches. ♪
♪ Why not? ♪
♪ I gotta bust a move ♪
♪ Drop and bust a groove ♪
♪ Feelin' fine. got an evil crew ♪
♪ Goldmember too ♪
♪ Lick my 9 ♪
♪ Till then I'll. on my butt ♪
♪ Brains out ♪
♪ Puton call and splooge in your that's all ♪
♪ Fo' shizzle my nizzle. y'all ♪
♪ Yeah. ♪
Alright. Listen up.
Tonight. 8 p.m..
you're going to start a riot.
Yes. Dr. Evil.
Attention. all guards.
There is a riot in progress.
Seal all exits.
Attention. Dr. Evil and his clone
are trying to escape.
All guards report
to Cell Block A immediately.
Dr. Evil and his clone are getting away.
There you are.
Good morning. sunshine.
Good morning.
How did you sleep?
Great.
Me too.
if these lips could talk.
Oh. hello.
You have the right to remain sexy. sugar.
I hope there is a search involved.
You've got mail.
So. what does this thing do?
Well. it's called the Internet
and it's completely revolutionized
the way we live
and access vital information.
For example. have a look at this.
Oh. look at the monkey.
Oh. he's got his finger on his...
Oh. no. watch out.
Now. that's vital information.
I know. it's amazing.
Oh. Basil.
What's happening. baby?
A lot is happening. Foxxy.
Dr. Evil has escaped.
The good news is that
one of our agents
has managed to infiltrate
Dr. Evil's organization.
Excellent Basil. we've been trying for years
to get a mole inside Dr. Evil's lair.
We now have that mole.
Yes.
And here he is.
So you're the...
Mo...
Most. Most.
Most.
Excellent agent we've ever seen.
Yes. most excellent agent
we've ever seen.
Thank you.
Now. I wasn't able to get an exact
location. but I did learn
that Dr. Evil has moved to a new lair
outside of Tokyo. Japan.
By the way. I realize
that I have a large mole on my face.
Where?
What?
Where's that mole?
I didn't see one.
I also realize the irony
that I am myself. a mole.
No one would make that connection.
Anyway. well done old chap.
Jolly good work.
Yes. nice to mole you...
Meet you. Nice to meet your mole.
Don't say mole.
Stop.
I said mole.
Bye.
Mole.
Stop.
Oh. shut up!
Moley-moley-moley-moley-moley.
Up. periscope.
Ladies and gentlemen.
welcome to my new submarine lair.
It's long and hard and full of seamen.
Nothing?
No?
Not even a titter?
Tough sub.
Dr. Evil. you look very tight.
Yes. tight like a tiger.
Yes. yes. yes.
Really?
Yes. you look like a macho man.
Village People.
You know. Goldmember
I don't think that's something
one dude should say to another dude.
Yeah.
A little creepy.
Oh. yes. yes. yes. yes.
This is a keeper.
Yes.
Alright. you're not gonna put
that skin in your mouth. are you?
You did.
Ok. that's just gross.
Yes. salty.
Yes. that was good.
Ladies and gentlemen.
as you know.
we've been designing
a tractor beam.
code-named Preparation H.
It's powerful enough
to pull the meteor.
Midas 22
into a collision course with the Earth.
Upon entering the atmosphere
the hot ball of magma.
will strike and melt the polar icecaps.
causing a global flood.
But enough of my technical
mumbo jumbo.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Lower the globe.
Lower the globe!
Well. congratulations. numbnuts.
You've succeeded in turning me
into a fricking jack-in-the-box.
Get it off. Get it off.
It's dark. it's dark.
I'm ok.
Release the meteor.
Release the meteor!
No way.
Right in the kniggin.
Goddamn it.
Guys.
Way to go. A-hole.
Alright. hold on.
While I try and find my balls.
for God's sakes.
One. two and three.
Ok. I'm ok.
Dr. Evil.
we still have the ultimate
insurance policy.
May I present to you.
the very sexual. the very tight.
Austin Powers' father.
His what?
His father. Dr. Evil.
His farger?
What's a farger?
His father. you know. the father.
Yeah Goldmember. I don't speak
freaky-deaky Dutch. ok. perv boy?
Father. His dad.
Dad is father.
Oh. his dad?
Oh. his father.
Yes. I have a Dutch accent.
Isn't that weird?
Father. Father.
Nigel Powers.
Hello. hello.
Bring him to me.
Easy peezy. lemon squeezy.
Put the guns down.
Is this.. Is this the first day on
the job or something?
Look. this is how it goes.
You attack me one at a time
and I knock you out
with a single punch.
Ok? Go.
Judo chop.
Oh. he's good.
Do you know who I am?
Have you any idea
how many anonymous henchmen
I've killed over the years?
And look at you.
You haven't even got a nametag.
You got no chance.
Why don't you just fall down?
Go on. son.
Alright. Dr. Evil.
give yourself up while
you've still got a chance.
Ok. Ok.
You've got me.
Nigel Powers.
meet...
Mini-Me.
Blimey.
I thought I smelled cabbage.
Take him away.
Dr. Evil. can I paint his yoo-hoo gold?
It's kind of my thing. you know.
How about no.
you crazy Dutch bastard?
Attention. henchmen.
it's health week.
Don't forget your physical.
Dr. Evil's orders.
You know. I think it's a shame
the way they treat you.
Just because you're
one-eighth their size.
Doesn't mean you deserve
one-eighth of their respect.
Does it?
Say. mini-fella. I'm...
I'm curious.
Is...
everything in proportion?
You know. your bobby-dangler.
your general. two colonels
your giggle stick.
master of ceremonies.
Oh. don't be shy.
Let's have a look.
My word.
You're a tripod.
What do you feed that thing?
It's like a baby's arm
holding an apple.
The good news is.
you ever get tired.
you can use it as a kickstand.
I think we both know who the real
brains is behind this operation?
Tokyo A Gogo. baby.
Yeah.
Oh. what's kicking. Basil?
A lot's kicking. Foxxy.
Austin.
one of Dr. Evil's henchmen. has been
spotted at the Asahi Sumo Arena.
Proceed there immediately.
Thanks. Basil.
Jesus Christ.
This diaper's making
my nuts rub together.
It's gonna start a fire.
That's Fat Bastard.
Fighter!
Fat Bastard.
You know what my favorite
Helen Hunt movie is?
Twister.
Fat Bastard winner.
Champion!
That's not right.
Sure ain't.
Are we done here?
I've got to take a crap.
Wait a tick.
Something doesn't smell right.
And I think it's Fat Bastard.
On top of spaghetti
All covered in...
Cheese.
I lost my poor meatball.
Because somebody...
You ok. Austin?
Sound as a pound. love.
Yeah. Good.
What the...
I didn't have any corn.
Hey. diaper lady.
Here's my diaper.
I think I might have pinched
one off too soon.
I left a rosebud in there for you.
You really are a fat bastard.
You know. that hurts my feelings.
I tried going on a diet. you know.
The Zone. You know.
carbs are the enemy?
We don't like carbs.
you know what I mean?
Who's your friend?
Oh. I'd like to have a go with that filly.
Oh. do you find me sexy?
Oh. look at my titties.
Shut your mouth.
Alright. that's enough.
Ok. you got me.
Put it there. would you?
Ok.
Come here. you.
My titties!
You gave me a nurple.
I've got you now.
Come here. you.
Prepare for the ultimate
wire-fighting maneuver.
I just hope my wire-fighting
team is ready.
Crikey.
Oh. great.
Isn't this magical?
One of my wires broke.
You under arrest. sugar.
Ok. Fat Bastard.
who's the Japanese cat
you made an exchange with?
Alright.
His name is Roboto.
He owns Roboto Industries.
He's designing some contraption
for Dr. Evil. I don't know.
The tractor beam.
That's it.
Listen...
Do you honestly think
that crime can pay?
Well. to be honest with you.
I've been trying to go legit.
I really take my sumo wrestling
seriously. you know.
But when you're an overweight child.
in a society that demands perfection.
well your sense of right. wrong.
fair and unfair.
will always be tragically skewed.
Did you just soil yourself?
Maybe...
It did sound a little wet. didn't it?
Right at the end.
Let's have a smell. alright?
Wafting. wafting.
Everyone likes their own brand. don't they?
This is magic.
Alright. analysis.
It smells like carrots and throw-up.
Oh. that could gag a maggot.
I smell like hot. sick ass
in a dead carcass.
Oh. even stink would say that stinks.
You know when you go
into an apartment building.
and you smell other people's cooking
on each floor and you go.
What are they cooking?
That. plus crap.
Hey. Pop.
Hey. Scotty.
How you been. sport?
I got you a present.
Really?
Open the tank.
Open the tank!
Are those sharks with laser beams
attached to their heads?
Cool.
You mean I actually
have fricking sharks
with fricking Laser beams
attached to their fricking heads?
You're the best evil son
an evil dad could ever ask for.
Well. I love you. Dad.
I love you. son.
It's touching moment. yes.
Scotty. come here.
Pop a squat right next to Daddy.
Mini-Me?
Move down the bench.
There's a power struggle. yes.
Scotty's on fire.
Alright. it's getting crowded in here.
Everyone out. everyone out.
Come on.
Not you. Scotty.
Not you. Number Two.
Not you. Frau.
Not you. Goldmember.
Not you. guys back there.
Not you. henchman holding wrench.
Not you henchman arbitrarily
turning knobs
making it seem like
you're doing something.
This is uncomfortable.
The tiny one can't take a hint.
He doesn't understand. he is small.
Hello. Foxxy. Austin.
We've confirmed what Fat Bastard
told you about Roboto is accurate.
He was hired by Dr. Evil
to construct Preparation H.
So Roboto had the technology
to build Goldmember's tractor beam.
Which means Roboto
will lead us to Goldmember.
Which means Goldmember
will lead us to my father.
You speak Japanese?
A little.
Well. you might be a cunning linguist.
but I'm a master debater.
I'm looking for my father.
he was kidnapped.
Please eat what?
Wait.
Tell me...
what do you know.
about my father's where.
abouts?
Your ass is happy?
No.
He said.
Nice potty mouth. dirtbag.
Yes. quite off topic.
thank you very much.
Why don't I just speak in English?
That would be a good idea.
now wouldn't it?
That way I wouldn't misread
the subtitles.
making it seem like
you're saying things that are dirty.
I'm sorry to hear about your father.
but I can't help you.
Please excuse me.
I have another appointment.
By the way...
Mr. Roboto is lying to us.
Tell me something I don't know.
I open-mouth kissed a horse once.
Say what?
That's something you don't know.
My spider sense is telling me
that my father's still in this building.
You keep a lookout.
I'm gonna try and sneak in.
Come on. come on. come on.
Judo chop!
Shazam!
Come on. sugar.
There's Goldmember and Roboto.
Yes. very impressive.
Put Preparation H
into my schtuppen transporten.
What's this?
You need this to turn on
the tractor beam.
It's a gold key.
It's gold.
Smarty-pants.
Let's spread out.
Yeah.
Hands up. Goldmember.
It's payback time.
Sure. you can kill me
but then...
what happens
to Austin Powers' father?
Dad.
Yes.
And now he's going to have
an unfortunate smelting accident.
Don't worry. Dad.
I'm here to rescue you.
May I point out that last time around.
you fell into an obvious trap.
Now you're trying to save me
instead of stopping Goldmember.
Oh. please. I'm not gonna
let Goldmember get away.
Austin. Goldmember's getting away.
Hello. hello.
Aren't you going to introduce us. Austin?
Foxxy. this is...
Powers. Nigel Powers.
Is that Eau de Flores you're wearing?
Yes. it is.
That's how a woman should smell.
Especially one as beautiful as you.
My. my.
Even in the face of danger.
you live up to your reputation.
Get on with it.
I've got an idea.
Your spy car's a MINI?
It's not the size mate.
it's how you use it.
You know I would've found
my way off that very well.
Fellas.
What?
I saved your life.
Listen.
You should've been doing your job.
Oh. you're welcome. man.
Shut up and turn around. please!
Run!
It's Godzilla!
It looks Like Godzilla.
but due to international
copyright laws. it's not.
Still we should run Like it is Godzilla!
Though it isn't.
There's Goldmember.
Breaker. breaker. 1-niner.
This is Goldy-Wang. Over.
10-4. there. Goldy-Wang.
This is Rubber Ducky.
What's your 10-20? Over.
I've got Preparation H in my rear
and Smokey the Bear in my back door.
We've got us a convoy. Over.
Copy that. you son of a bitch
pile of monkey nuts.
Open wide there. Rubber Ducky.
I am entering your mouth now. Over.
Great. Goldmember got away.
Now what?
I think it's obvious.
We should take Dr. Evil's lair by force.
You can be my backup. son.
Backup?
Well. that's fairly condescending.
Do you think Dr. Evil's
gonna expect an attack?
We should infiltrate his lair.
This ain't my first rodeo. cowboy.
We need commandos.
scuba. gadgets for God's sake.
Well. I don't like to use gadgets.
outside the bedroom.
I thank you.
Outside the bedroom.
You know. I think being frozen
damaged your brain.
Really?
And how would you know?
This is the most time that
we've ever spent together since...
ever.
What are you saying. son?
Oh. please.
What boy learned to drive a car
with machine guns on it?
Or had a helicopter
you can fit in a knapsack?
What about your Swedish nanny. Helga?
Oh. yes.
Helga.
Let's say I didn't hire her
for the cooking.
Oh. yes.
She stayed on until you were 24.
We were mates. you and I.
I didn't need a friend.
I needed a father.
Do you know I risked
my life trying to save you
and you still don't give
me any respect.
Respect. oh come on.
If you've got an issue.
here's a tissue.
That is not funny.
Well...
I suppose we better go
our separate ways. then.
Fine.
So I've been assigned to welcome you
to the Ministry of Defence.
I have a letter from my director
personally thanking you for switching sides.
I...
can't wait to inform Austin
of your defection.
Hello Basil.
Yes. Austin should be here any second.
Yes.
Yes. I'm in Austin's hotel
room right now.
Assassin!
Try to kill me. will you?
Oh. you want to be friends?
Wait a tick.
Peace?
I'm not falling for that again.
But at least he didn't mention it.
Yes. I realize he can't talk.
Listen. I think Dr. Evil treated him badly
and that's why he's decided to help us.
Come back here. you little bugger.
Got you.
Oh. yes. I'm sure Austin and Mini
will get along famously.
No. I guarantee nothing will happen
to Mini-Me on my watch.
Come on. you bugger.
Come on. I got you.
Oh. I think he and Austin will be united
in their commitment to stopping Dr. Evil.
Austin. there you are.
I've come to tell you the good news.
Mini-Me has...
switched sides.
Sorry about that. old chap.
Sorry.
You know. Sorry.
Welcome aboard.
My mole-stake.
What was that?
Listen. just get it out of your system.
No. I'm fine.
I insist. I saw clearly...
We could work together better if you don't...
Mole! Bloody mole!
We're not supposed to talk
about the bloody mole but
there is a bloody mole
winking me in the face.
I'm gonna chop it off
and cut it up and make
some guacamole.
Better?
Yeah.
So you've decided to join us. Mini-Me?
Welcome to the good side.
my mini-brother.
And thank you for the map
of Dr. Evil's sub.
What's this?
It says.
Dr. Evil's tractor beam is now complete.
There's not much time.
Dr. Evil must pay.
You are so beautiful.
Are you a clone of an angel?
That is so sweet.
Well no. my mini-man. I'm not.
Are you sure you don't have
a little clone in you?
Yeah. I'm sure.
Would you like to?
Horny bugger.
That is so not funny.
Ok. everyone. prepare to dive.
This spy car's also a submarine.
Get me the World Organization.
What is it. Dr. Evil?
Gentlemen. in a matter of hours
a meteor will crash into Earth.
causing a global flood.
That is of course. unless you pay me.
one billion
million yen.
I think you're bluffing.
Well. perhaps you'd like a demonstration.
Number Two. the key please.
Sir. Dr. Evil's not bluffing.
One of our satellites
is falling out of orbit.
Which one?
It's the one that looks like a pair of...
Melons.
Big. juicy melons.
Are they nice and firm?
Well. what do you think?
Look at that.
It looks like a set of giant...
Hey. A and N. you're late.
How we doing? We're back.
Go. Titans!
Check it out.
Those remind me of...
Boobs.
Boobs. Ozzy?
These filmmakers are just ♫ boobs.
What do you mean. Dad?
Why they're using the same ♫ joke
as they did in the last Austin Powers movie.
What ♫ joke?
You know ♫
joke about the long smooth rocket
that looks like some guy's...
Johnson?
Yes. sir.
Any sign of that satellite?
No. sir. It's gone.
Gentlemen. you have my demands.
Peace out.
Cor. baby.
You look very switched on.
Thank you. Austin.
No. Mini-Me. Off. Bad.
Mustn't. No humping.
Dr. Evil.
in light of the success of the device.
it is Japanese custom
that I receive a bonus.
A bonus?
That's good.
Yeah. that's awesome.
Throw me a fricking bonus here.
I haven't laughed that hard
since I was a little girl. thank you.
You're not joking.
No in fact. if you don't give me the bonus...
Hey. Dad.
Hey Scotty. how are you sport?
Why don't you let me take care of this?
Ok.
He's got a good evil laugh.
Get along.
Scotty!
Scotty.
Take it down a notch.
It's creeping a bit.
Let's go.
We'll need a disguise.
There's only one uniform.
One of us has to go on
the other one's shoulders.
Hey there. buddy. How's it going?
Good to see you.
Yeah. Yeah. Hi.
How are you?
Just getting my sea legs.
Sorry about that.
Hello.
You alright?
Yes. it's a good hat.
Very good hat.
Come on. Mini-Me.
Let's go.
Hold it right there. mister.
Did you really think you could
get away with this?
I did. actually. Yes.
Every new recruit must have a physical.
Now get in here. sailor.
I'm going to need a urine sample.
Ok.
No.
I don't know.
Ok. then.
Ok.
Hello.
And here we go.
Sorry.
Right.
There you go. Right.
Yes.
Terrific.
Yes. good.
Ok.
Alright sailor.
go behind that screen and...
strip down to your skivvies.
Alright. then.
I'll just go to that screen
which is over there.
Right behind that screen.
Next.
Come on. hurry.
The map.
Ok. what's our plan?
I'm going to need a urine sample.
Ok.
Which way to the main chamber?
Ok. so.
Oh. sure.
Excuse me. doctor?
It's difficult in public. isn't it?
Mini-Me. our shadows.
We're casting a shadow.
What's wrong. sailor?
You should check that guy out.
What the hell's going on here?
Hands up.
You heard me I said hands up.
Both of you.
Come with me.
Mini-Me. the map. Go.
Ok.
You got me.
Are you alright. little man?
Right on.
Mr. Powers.
Before I kill you.
perhaps you'd like to see
the genius of my plan.
Key. please.
What the...
Who? But how? Where?
Looking for this?
Mini-Me?
Alright.
everybody drop your guns.
because Foxxy Cleopatra's in the sub.
Smashing. Foxxy.
Yeah.
Here. sugar.
Alright. Dr. Evil.
It's finally come down to this.
You. me and a gun.
What are you going
to do now. Austin?
Dad?
What are you doing here?
I've gotta finish this off
once and for all.
I'm afraid you can't do that.
I have to protect my son.
Dad. I'm fine.
I'm not talking about you.
I'm talking about...
him.
What?
Dr. Evil's not your son. I am.
You both are.
What?
It was our first...
family holiday together.
Just as I was finishing a case.
your mother brought the two
of you to Belgium.
I stopped to have a tinkle...
when the car.
But. my parents died in a car accident.
It was no accident.
It was an assassination attempt.
I thought only Austin survived.
I should have told you the truth earlier.
but those Belgians.
they made you so damn...
evil.
Of course...
they share a border with the Dutch.
Very interesting story. Mr. Powers.
Of course. I'm gonna have to wait
until I see all the facts.
Daddy.
Daddy's here. Dougie.
Dougie?
Dougie. Remember. Dougie?
Dad. what's going on?
What are you going to do. Austin?
Austin.
Are you sure you can trust Dr. Evil?
He ain't heavy.
he's my brother. baby.
Yeah.
I should have told you
this so long ago. son.
I'm very proud of you.
Can you forgive me?
I forgive you. Dad.
Come on.
Yes.
My two sons.
I'm Dougie.
Come on.
Oh. there you are.
Oh. come on.
I mean. first I'm not evil enough for you.
And now you're gonna turn good?
Listen. Scott.
You can spend your whole life
trying to win your parents'
acceptance. believe me.
But at the end of the day.
you've just gotta do it for yourself. baby.
That all I've gotta do?
Hey. Austin?
What?
I hate you.
I don't even know you.
but I hate you too.
And I especially hate you.
You'll pay.
You'll all pay.
I'd like to point out that no one else
in my gene pool runs like a girl.
Not so fast. smarty-pants.
Dr. Evil.
you might not want to destroy the world.
but I do.
Preparation H goes ahead as planned.
I'm going to flood the Earth.
Think again. Goldmember.
Foxxy Cleopatra.
It's a shame I had to kill your partner.
Too bad for you.
Too bad for me?
How about too bad for you?
Oh. no.
No! No! No!
No.
Luckily. I keep a spare.
Look. everyone.
My winkie was a key.
Only a bloody Dutchman.
You mine. sucker.
Yes.
Foxxy. I'm coming.
Nobody try anything stupid
or the shooting begins.
Austin. take Dougie.
I'll stay here and be your backup.
Dougie. what do we do?
I'm not a real hands-on evil genius.
Think. you were always the smart one.
I could reroute the output capacitor
to the tractor beam
from one of the conduit boxes up there.
Come on. let's go.
Yes. the shooting begins.
Let me shoot.
You know. Dr. Evil
I used to think you were crazy.
I know.
But now I can see you're nuts.
I thank you.
Give me the gun.
Hurry.
Father. Father. Father.
Father. Father.
Father. can you hear me?
Well done. Austin.
He saved the world again.
Hey. yeah.
Thank you.
Right on.
Yeah.
Austin. you did it.
We did it.
Yeah. baby.
No?
Just trying it on.
Goldmember?
You under arrest. sugar.
Assholes.
Do I have time for a last smoke
and a pancake or what?
I am from Holland.
Isn't that weird?
Yeah.
Yes. well done.
Good on you. man.
Thank you.
Yes.
Hey. Powers.
Fat Bastard?
But you're not fat anymore.
I went on the Subway diet.
You know. just like Jared.
I've lost 180 pounds.
Congratulations. baby.
Thank you.
I do have a little bit
of excess skin. though.
Bit of a problem here. yeah.
And unfortunately.
my neck does look like a vagina.
Austin! Austin!
Over here.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Austin. you the boss!
You alright?
Loved it!
Ok.
Austin.
Thank you for everything.
Shazam.
I'm gonna get you. Austin Powers.
By LESAIGNEUR
Sync & corrections June 2019
Well. they're using the same ♫ joke
as they did in the last Austin Powers film.
Movie... What was it?
Well. they're using the... Well...
Well. they're using the same
joke that they did...
What do I mean?
Boobs. Ozzy.
Stop. do that again.
You're starting to laugh.
Oh. don't start. Kelly. so
or I'll put you back in the refrigerator.
One more.
I don't like that.
A little serious.
Don't make that noise. Sharon.
I'm getting turned on.
My testosterone is going dancing.
Get off me.
Is... Is it true what
they say about you?
Kickstand.
Really?
Can I give you
my cell phone number?
Please?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Mr. Burt Bacharach.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today